{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Laminate Countertop Repair Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40021/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40021,"taskName":"Laminate Countertops - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Laminate Countertops","xmTaskDescriptor":"Laminate Countertop Repair Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":52,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"formica counter corian laminate coran","textMessagingName":"Repr Lamnte Counter","rolloverLongDesc":"Generically called laminate countertops, they are the most popular kind of countertops.  Come in huge variety of colors \u0026 patterns with \u0026 without splashblocks at the rear edge.  Made of hard plastic glued onto chipboard.  Many consider it less luxurious than solid surface countertops like Corian.","rolloverShortDesc":"Most common kind of countertops.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Laminate Countertops.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Laminate Countertop Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Laminate Counters","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":8,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Laminate Countertop Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Laminate Countertops - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Laminate Countertop Project","urlName":"Laminate-Countertops-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Laminate Countertop Repair Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"formica,counter,corian,laminate,coran,countertop","emcCategoryOid":-12016,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":345,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40021/":{"taskOID":40021,"originalTaskOID":40021,"setID":345,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":265,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description(s) of the countertop problem you need repaired.  (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5500,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Scratch","answerDisplayText":"Scratch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1687,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Crack","answerDisplayText":"Crack","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1867,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Delaminating","answerDisplayText":"Delaminating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1193,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Burn","answerDisplayText":"Burn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1148,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bubble","answerDisplayText":"Bubble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1382,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Chip","answerDisplayText":"Chip","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1940,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":265,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description(s) of the countertop problem you need repaired.  (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5500,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Scratch","answerDisplayText":"Scratch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1687,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Crack","answerDisplayText":"Crack","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1867,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Delaminating","answerDisplayText":"Delaminating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1193,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Burn","answerDisplayText":"Burn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1148,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bubble","answerDisplayText":"Bubble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1382,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Chip","answerDisplayText":"Chip","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1940,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5500,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Scratch","answerDisplayText":"Scratch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1687,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Crack","answerDisplayText":"Crack","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1867,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Delaminating","answerDisplayText":"Delaminating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1193,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Burn","answerDisplayText":"Burn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1148,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bubble","answerDisplayText":"Bubble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1382,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Chip","answerDisplayText":"Chip","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1940,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}